Listen, I get it.
They're enemies of Western civilization.
Who are these people?
Are they the Muslims?
Are they the Jews?
Are they, you know, whatever people have values?
No, no, no.
They're not the Muslims.
They're not the Jews.
They're not the blacks.
They're not whatever group you're blaming.
They're any individual who doesn't acknowledge the human soul.
It feels like a shift of positivity when you see folks who you know have been agents of deception,
agents of oppression, agents of animosity, changing course.
It seems like, oh, they figured it out.
They've learned.
If they have not atoned, if they have not acknowledged from whence they came, the damage that they've
caused, their role in priming the soil with the toxins necessary for these same bad actors
they're talking about to take root, then it is not enough.
And you might say, but why?
It's not just an act of accountability.
It is because there has to be restorative justice practices.
There has to be an actual muscle work.
There has to be an actual application of work to change the cellular structure internally
that allowed you to be even on that mess in the first place.
And it's not just going to shift because you're under pressure now.
It can't just be a shift in behavior.
It has to be a shift in the core.
There is a privilege in simply just switching course and not having to name why.
And not having to apologize.
There is an ego death that has to happen to be truly a vessel.
And when we platform these people because they've all of a sudden started talking in a way that
makes sense to us without making that demand of them, we are completely disregarding how
much it has taken for us to exist in this space while they were agents of our own destruction.
I'll quote Cameron, your whole crew, switch-siders.
I come through, they be like, hey, Cam, dick riders.
Stop letting people switch sides without making them accountable for the side they was on.
It does a disservice to the actual spiritual and physical work of change
that is going to be required to make anything we're doing sustainable.
Thank you.